A Finding Aid to the Chuck and Jan Rosenak Research Material, circa 1938-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.rosechuc
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Material, circa 1990s; Series 5; (Boxes 13-18; 4.5 linear ft.)
  - Photographs and Negatives for The Saint Makers: Contemporary Santeras y Santeros, circa 1990s; 5.3
    - Brito, Frank, Sr. (Box 17, Folder 108)
      (2 contact sheets and negatives; 4 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Frank Brito, Sr., Margarito R. Mondragon)
    - Carrillo, Charlie, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 4 photos) (Box 17, Folder 109)
    - Cash, Marie Romero, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 5 photos) (Box 17, Folder 110)
    - Cordova, Gloria López (Box 17, Folder 111)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Gloria López Cordova, Marco A. Oviedo, Cruzito (Cruz) Flores, Frank Alarid)
    - Cordova, James, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 4 photos) (Box 17, Folder 112)
    - Esquibel, José Raul (Box 17)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Catherine Robles-Shaw)
    - Flores, Cruzito (Cruz) (Box 17, Folder 114)
      (2 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Cruziot (Cruz) Flores, Joseph Felix and Krissa Maria López, Krissa Maria López, and Joseph A. López; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Cordova)
    - Goler, Gustavo Victor (Box 17, Folder 115)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Gustavo Victor Goler and Bernadette Pino; 5 photos)
    - Herrera, Nicholas (Box 18, Folder 1)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Nicholas Herrera, Ernie R. Lujan, Leroy L. Trujillo; 6 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Lusito Luhan)
    - Jaramillo, Rubel U. (Box 18, Folder 2)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Rubel U. Jaramillo, Carlos A. Santistevan; 4 photos)
    - Jones, Anita Romero (Box 18, Folder 3)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Anita Romero Jones, Fernando Bimonte; 2 photos)
    - López, Félix A, (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Flores; 3 photos) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - López, José Benjamin, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Luisito Luhan) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - López, Joseph A., (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Flores; 3 photos) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Lopez, Krissa (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - López, Krissa Maria, Joseph A. and Felix, (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Flores; 2 photos) (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - López, Peter, (3 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Mondgragon) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - López, Ramón José, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 8 photos; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Frankie Nazario Lucero) (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - López, Raymond (Ray) (Box 18, Folder 11)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Raymond (Ray) López, Jacobo de la Serna; 4 photos)
    - Lucero, David Nabor, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 6 photos) (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Lucero, David Nabor and Kim, (4 photos) (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Lucero, Frankie Nazario (Box 18, Folder 14)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Frankie Nazario Lucero, José and Frankie Lucero, Jacob Martinez, Ramon López; 1 photo)
    - Lucero, José, (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Frankie Nazario Lucero; 1 photo) (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Lucero, José and Frankie Nazerio, (3 photos) (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Lujan, Ernie R., (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Herrera; 3 photos) (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Lujan, Jerome, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 5 photos) (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Lujan, Luisito (Box 18, Folder 19)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Luisito Luhan, José Benjamin López, Nicholas Herrera; 4 photos)
    - Martinez, Jacob, (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Frankie Nazario Lucero; 2 photos) (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Mondragon, Margarito R. (Box 18, Folder 21)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Brito; 1 contact sheet and negatives: Margarito R. Mondragon, Peter López; 3 photos)
    - Ortega, Eulogio, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 2 photos) (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Ortega, Eulogio and Zoraida, (2 photos) (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Ortiz, Sabinita Lopez (Box 18, Folder 24)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Sabinita Lopez Ortiz, Marco A. Oviedo; 2 photos)
    - Otero, Alcario, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 3 photos) (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Oviedo, Marco A., (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Cordova; 1 contact sheet and negatives, see Ortiz; 6 photos) (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Pino (de Goler), Bernadette, (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Goler; 1 photo) (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Robles-Shaw, Catherine (Box 18, Folder 28)
      (1 contact sheet and negatives: Catherine Robles-Shaw, José Raul Esquibel; 4 photos)
    - Santistevan, Carlos A., (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Jaramillo; 2 photos) (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Sena, Arlene Cisneros, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 5 photographs) (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Serna, Jacobo de la, (1 contact sheet and negatives, see López; 4 photos) (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Tapia, Luis, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 3 photos) (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Trujillo, Leroy L., (1 contact sheet and negatives, see Herrera; 3 photos) (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Withers, Malcolm, (1 contact sheet and negatives; 3 photos) (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 18, Folder 35)